But you also experiment a little bit with actual DMT as well. I absolutely.
Can you describe.
That experience?
I listen it's really.
Crazy.
This is my partner. This.
Is my partner I'm doing the GM.
And my part is right here and then I used.
To like the sun opens up. And I feel like the fucking boom, the sun over and the air.
Cost. Do you see that to see what I.
Hear it? I think they're playing tricks. I think because my crew likes to prank me all the time is I think they're pranking mess. I know you.
See this shit.
Don'T.
You either, Mike? I don't.
See how long did that last.
That'S.
For a minute, what literally one minute? Not like no for a minute sometime for.
20 minutes. Also.
Delis like that, though, are also if you take one too many mushrooms. The sun opens up. I don't think like that. Okay.
We also do the total we experience with the time.
Yeah.
So what did.
You smoke you smoke the venom on the back of a toad. Or how does it work? But it's not like the.
Rest of we smoking your active. You can.
Be active.
As soon as you take the hit. Boom, your soul goes here and your body goes here. Oh.
No here in the United States for that. As well, or is that a Mexico I've done in.
Mexico? I.
Think Chihuahua is one of the precincts and.
The Mexico.
Great crazy and that's like that's the highest right, can you go above the toad? They say no, but the.
Lizard tail is very close. The snake venom is very close to white. Corp is very close.
How did you figure this out that's the history that is the first time is a snake.
Let'S.
Smoke, it no history.
Told us what happened. This is what happened they saw an animal attacks. I forgot what animal was. But it was an animal player. Attack it and they started acting weird and trembling and.
Without and.
They thought it was pointed then 20 minutes. He came back up and just.
Took off.
And so the Native American food at. And they sort of didn't die that you won't back up. And I guess that's how to experience.
That actually makes sense that doesn't make a lot actually makes sense. But what is that feeling like, for you.
To leave your body.
Like, do you actually feel like you left your body?
It's the most scariest experience for everything go through in their lives. To not that you're dead. Hey, man, I don't want to do that. I do want to do that. Listen in life. Do you just want to be you? Right now, do you want to be this way to the day you die? No, you think working on it? No, but do you want to be like this? To the day you die the same mentality. The same way you think about life the same way you think about humanity right now, you want to stop right here I want to move forward, but that's what the to does? It.
Actually makes you move sideways it's not forward. I say this all the time to people I say what if someone told you that there was a way to see life in a completely different way, where up wasn't up and right wasn't right. And everything was different you wouldn't want to at least experience that 1-2-1 before you pass.
Go deeper. That experience being God for a few minutes that's what it does introduce you to God. What are you thinking on one basis that's.
What people say?
Georgie.
Listen I'm not encouraging I'm glad you as a person in my standing, I have to actually it didn't go so well done in 16 times the toad. What do you mean? Will you see God.
Like.
You see him or you're equal to him.
Okay.
So you're equal to got.
It. I don't think.
George is gonna like that he's a very he's no, very big Christian man no, no.
This is bigger than religion.
Right?
And.
Also, I don't this.
Is Dian. This is time. This is letting this stuff. You see your ancestors want to be some answers you want to meet people who died. Recently you love handle it. The total it takes you way back, buddy. This.
Is scary I'm not sure I want that smoke. I don't know if I can handle it. Is there any God forbid? If you do.
Like a tiny bit too much die.
You can't die from it, I okay, so it's just a for sure experience.
And if you look at medically, it took people off of drugs to stop people from being Hispanic.
Depressed.